25/02/2024, 15:01 New Resume | Resume Editor

Rearrange Sections

×

ANJALI PAWAR

Full Stack Developer

+91 8369278129

@ anjalipawar2206@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/anjali-pawar-4917611a6/

∂ https://github.com/Anjali2206/

☆ https://portfolio-anjalip.netlify.app/

SUMMARY

A skilled Frontend Developer with 2+ years of experience, specializing in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript with expertise in React for building modern, responsive web applications. Experienced in the Banking domain, Committed to delivering exceptional user experiences and staying updated with emerging technologies.

SKILLS



EXPERIENCE

Virtusa - Software Engineer

05/2022 - Present

1. Client Off-Boarding Application

- Developed Banking client off-boarding application using React.Js
- This ensures a seamless experience for clients transitioning out of the system, optimizing navigation and scalability.
- Implemented Atomic design pattern which helped to create more consistent UI with better maintainability.
- Used Redux-Thunk to manage global state and asynchronous logic within Redux and used (ES6)
 JavaScript on top of micro-frontend architecture.
- Used Module federation to build scalable, modular applications by facilitating the seamless integration of independently developed modules introducing dynamic routing.
- Performed extensive unit tests using Jest and react-testing-library.
 Worked in Agile methodologies for incremental development to deliver better application.

08/2021 - 04/2022

2. Client On-Boarding Application

- Maintained on-boarding application which is built on ReactJs, Redux-Thunk, and Hooks.
 This application focuses on creating a responsive and efficient on-boarding experience.
- This application focuses on creating a responsive and efficient on-boarding experience for clients.
 Boosted performance by 30% Using advanced features like debouncing and memoization.
- Boosted performance by 30% using advanced reatures like debouncing and r
 Implemented shimmer UI to enhance user experience during content loading.
- Extensively used Json for dynamic component rendering in react.
 Worked closely with back-end developers to integrate RESTful APIs and implement efficient data fetching
- strategies.

 Pefactored the code for better efficiency, readability, and performance. Pecolved vulnerability issues.
- · Refactored the code for better efficiency, readability, and performance. Resolved vulnerability issues.

EDUCATION

07/2016 - 10/2020

B.E in Electronics & Telecommunication

MGM College of Engineering and Technology, Kamothe, Navi Mumbai.

PROJECTS

PERSONAL PROJECTS

- 1. HungerHub (Swiggy Clone) : React-Based Food Ordering App
- Built highly scalable, responsive app using React, JavaScript, Tailwind CSS, Redux, Parcel.
- 2. Netflix Clone: Responsive Movie Watching And Recommendation App

An Innovative Movie App Powered by React, Redux, Tallwind, ESBuild, and OpenAl for Lightning-Fast Loading and Responsive Performance.

TRAINING / COURSES

Exam AZ-900: Microsoft Azure Fundaments

React Js [From NamasteReact]

Young Star of the Year Award2023

www.enhancv.com

Powered by Enhancy